Guide to the James Rockwell Sheffield Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
James Rockwell Sheffield papers
1768-1969
MS 446
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
9.75
The papers consist of correspondence, scrapbooks, writings, and photographs documenting the political and diplomatic career of James Rockwell Sheffield. The bulk of the material dates from 1893 to 1938 and concerns either the New York Republican party and its influence on National politics or American diplomatic relations with Mexico during the Coolidge administration. Major correspondents include William Boyd Allison, Nicholas Murray Butler, Theodore Roosevelt, Elihu Root, William Howard Taft, and James R. Wadsworth.
Sheffield, James R. (James Rockwell), 1864-1938
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Frederick Sheffield, 1957; and James R. Sheffield, 1990, 2002.
Scope and Contents
The James Rockwell Sheffield Papers consist of correspondence, writings, scrapbooks, photographs, and memorabilia documenting the political and diplomatic career of James R. Sheffield, a New York City lawyer, Republican Party and civic leader, and ambassador to Mexico during the Coolidge administration. The papers, a 1957 gift of Frederick Sheffield to the Yale University Library, span the dates 1768-1969 and include family memorabilia from Saybrook, Connecticut. The bulk of the papers date from 1893 to 1938.
The papers are arranged in three series: I. CORRESPONDENCE, 1768-1969; II. SCRAPBOOKS, 1893-1940; III. PERSONAL PAPERS, 1868-1938.
Series I includes James R. Sheffield's political and diplomatic correspondence as well as correspondence of other family members. Series II contains scrapbooks which document Sheffield's entire political and diplomatic career. Series III, which is the smallest of the series, is composed of biographical material, memorabilia, subject files, and Sheffield's writings.
Series I, CORRESPONDENCE, is divided into four sections: General; Letterpress copybooks; Family; and Miscellanea. The first two sections span Sheffield's long career in public life and trace his friendships, political training, and party alliances. They also concern Sheffield's civic and Yale alumni interests and personal family business. There are no letters concerning Sheffield's legal practice or the law firm of Sheffield and Betts. Only a few letters to family members appear in the papers. General correspondence is arranged in chronological order and consists of both incoming and outgoing letters, though in the beginning of the section there are only scattered copies of outgoing letters. A list of selected correspondents is included in this register as an appendix. Letterpress copybooks contains bound copies of Sheffield's outgoing letters for the period 1914-1916 and 1920. Each volume contains an index of correspondents.
General files begin with letters from Sheffield's political mentor and close personal friend, Senator William Boyd Allison of Iowa. From the early 1890s, when Sheffield began his law practice in New York City, there are notifications of meetings and political literature showing Sheffield's interest in the Republican Party and the Good Government Club movement. The correspondence throughout the 1890s is dominated by political topics including Sheffield's successful campaign for the New York Assembly (1893), constituent mail and advice from Republican leaders such as Elihu Root, on legislation, particularly civil service re-form (1894), and letters concerning Sheffield's service on the New York City Board of Fire Commissioners (1895-1897).
While Sheffield served on the Fire Commission, he formed a close association with Theodore Roosevelt, who was then on the Police Commission. Letters from Roosevelt date from his service on the Police Commission through two presidential terms. Sheffield wrote Roosevelt regarding New York appointments, tariff reform, the 1904 reelection campaign, and his own desire for a political appointment.
Beginning with folder 27, there are letters showing Sheffield's 1908 campaign efforts to nominate and elect William Howard Taft as Roosevelt's successor. The files from 1908 to the end of the correspondence contain many exchanges with Taft. Letters in folder 33 explain Sheffield's support for Taft's reelection and his break with Roosevelt in 1912.
Folders 33-35 contain many letters from Supreme Court Justice Edward Douglass White. These same folders document Sheffield's service as president of the National Republican Club. Sheffield supported the nomination of Elihu Root in 1916, and the files attest to his work on Root's behalf. He eventually campaigned for the party nominee Charles Evans Hughes. Correspondence with both Hughes and Root continues into the 1930s. Sheffield's outgoing letters during his term as president of the National Republican Club are contained in five letterpress copybooks (boxes 8-9).
Numerous letters from Nicholas Murray Butler, Charles Dewey Hilles, and James R. Wadsworth begin in 1919. In 1920 Sheffield attended the Republican convention as a supporter of Butler for president. He also chaired Wadsworth's successful senatorial campaign. Letters from these years comment on convention politics, campaign issues, and the problems facing Republican politicians over the enforcement of the Volstead Act. One letterpress copybook (folder 79) primarily concerns the Wadsworth campaign.
Beginning with folder 47, the primary subject of the correspondence shifts from Republican politics to American relations with Mexico. In 1924 Sheffield was appointed ambassador to Mexico, a position he held through 1927. The correspondence is most extensive for the years 1926-1927 (folders 49-55). As ambassador Sheffield responded to the Calles government's nationalization of American property, and he staunchly defended American property rights. The correspondence demonstrates Sheffield's efforts to explain the situation to Secretary of State Frank Kellogg and President Calvin Coolidge and his frustration with a perceived lack of support from the Coolidge administration. Frequent correspondents at the time include Chandler P. Anderson, H. F. Arthur Schoenfeld, and Yale classmate William Lyon Phelps. Following Sheffield's resignation in 1927, there are exchanges with Robert E. Olds, Alexander W. Weddell, and Sheffield's successor, Dwight Morrow, on the situation in Mexico.
Sheffield held one other diplomatic appointment. In 1930 he served as a special ambassador to Venezuela on the occasion of the dedication of a Henry Clay statue. There are letters concerning travel arrangements and Sheffield's report on the celebration.
The correspondence from 1930 until Sheffield's death in 1938 includes discussions of Republican prospects in the 1932 and 1936 elections. There are also Sheffield's reminiscences of Senator Allison and Elihu Root which he wrote for biographers. On the occasion of Sheffield's 70th birthday in 1934 there are numerous letters of congratulation from colleagues, friends, and politically prominent people of the day, while folder 71 contains a few letters of condolence after Sheffield's death.
The Family and Miscellanea sections contain correspondence and items relating to Sheffield's family and others. Material relating to Frederick William Hotchkiss, Sheffield's great-grandfather, concerns Saybrook, Connecticut and the Congregational church he led there in the late 18th and early 19th centuries. Letters to Sheffield's parents, Frederick William and Sarah Kellogg Sheffield, include several from William Boyd Allison. The files for Sheffield's son Frederick Sheffield contain many letters of greeting to James R. Sheffield on his 70th birth-day. Folders 97-99 consist of letters to non-family members. Some of these are addressed to Oliver Jennings and D. B. Delevan as financial agents in Sheffield's 1893 election campaign. Also included are letters of introduction and testimonials written for a 1915 dinner honoring Sheffield.
Series II, SCRAPBOOKS, is composed of fifteen scrapbook volumes, which begin in 1893 and span Sheffield's subsequent political and diplomatic career. The scrapbooks contain newspaper clippings, as well as campaign publicity, printed material, invitations, correspondence, photographs, and other types of memorabilia. They are particularly thorough in their coverage of the 1893 election, civil service reform legislation authored by Sheffield, the New York City Fire Commission during Sheffield's tenure, and Sheffield's tour of duty as ambassador to Mexico. Folder 117 contains an album of photographs from Mexico and Venezuela as well as family pictures.
Series III, PERSONAL PAPERS, contains biographical material, memorabilia, subject files on New York politics, and Sheffield's writings. Folder 118 includes a 79-page memoir by Sheffield which details his service in Mexico and a 44-page autobiographical sketch. Additional biographical material can be found in the memorials included in folder 119 and the obituaries in folder 136. Folders 131-132 contain political memorabilia similar to that found in the scrapbooks. The series also includes typed and printed copies of Sheffield's writings, primarily his speeches, which affirm his reputation as a toastmaster and banquet speaker.
Biographical / Historical
James Rockwell Sheffield practiced law in New York City. He was active in Republican politics and served in the New York legislature, on the New York City Board of Fire Commissioners, as president of the National Republican Club, and as a delegate to four Republican national conventions between 1916 and 1936. From 1924 to 1927 Sheffield was United States Ambassador to Mexico.
SELECT LIST OF CORRESPONDENTS TO JAMES ROCKWELL SHEFFIELD
Abbott, Lawrence Fraser 1859-1933
Adee, George Townsend 1874-
Adler, Julius. Och 1896-1935
Aiken, Alfred Lawrence 1870-1946
Aldridge, George W.
Alexander, Helen Manice
Alexander, James W. 1839-1915
Allison, William Boyd 1829-1908
Anderson, Chandler Parson 1866-1936
Angell, James Rowland 1869-1949
Auchincloss, Hugh Dudley 1858-1913
Austin, George C.
Baker, Newton Diehl 1871-1937
Baldwin, Elbert Francis 1857-1927
Bannard, Otto Tremont 1854-1929
Barnes, William (Jr.] 1860-1930
Barton, George De Forest
Basham, Harvey A
Bates, Lindell Theodore, 1890-1937
Baylor, Theodore T
Betts, Frederic Henry 1843-1905
Betts, Samuel Rossiter 1786-1868
Bingham, Hiram 1875-1956
Bliss, Conrelius Newton 1833-1911
Bonner, Hugh -1908
Boswell, Helen Varick
Bradford, Standish
Bridgman, Oliver B.
Bristow, W. B.
Brock, John W., Jr.
Brownell, Herbert [Jr.] 1904-
Buell, Raymond Leslie 1896-1946
Bulkley, Sarah Tod
Bullard, Robert Lee 1861-
Burleigh, George William 1870-1940
Butler, Nicholas Murray 1862-1947
Butler, William Morgan 1861-1937
Cady, J. Cleveland -1919
Calder, Frederick M.
Calhoun, Henry Warner 1862-1906
Camp, Walter Chauncey 1859-1925
Campbell, Alexander V.
Carpenter, Fred Warner 1873-
Carter, Ernest
Carter, George Robert 1866-1933
Caruna, George J.
Castle, William R., Jr.
Chittenden, Alice Hill
Choate, Joseph Hodges 1832-1917
Clark, John Kirkland
Clarke, John Proctor 1856-1932
Coffin, Henry Sloane 1877-1954
Collis, Charles H.T. 1838-1902
Conkling, Alfred Ronalds 1850-1917
Constantine, Arthur
Conway, George R. G.
Coolidge, Calvin, Pres. U.S. 1872-1933
Coolidge, Grace Anna (Goodhue) 1879-1957
Coolidge, Louis Arthur 1861-1925
Cortelyou, George Bruce 1862-1940
Couple, Leo O
Cowles, William Hutchinson 1866-1946
Crane, Frederick Evan 1889-1947
Cravath, Paul Drennan 1861-1940
Crocker, William Henry 1861-1937
Croker, Edward F
Cromwell, George 1860-1943
Cross, Wilbur Lucius 1862-1948
Crowder, Enoch Herbert 1859-1932
Crozier, William 1855-1942
Curtiss, Julian Wheeler 8-1944
Cuyler, Thomas DeWitt 4-1922
Daniels, Josephus 1862-1948
Darlington, Henry
Daugherty, Harry Micajah 1860-1941
Davidson, William C
Davis, John William 1873-1955
Davis, Manton 1876-
Davison, Charles Stewart 1855-1942
Davison, Henry Pomeroy 1867-1922
Dawes, Charles Gates 1865-1951
Day, Benjamin Mulford 1886-
Day, George Parmly 1876-1959
Depew, Chauncey Mitchell 1834-1928
Doan, John D
Dwight, Timothy 1828-1916
Dye, Alexander V.
Eagle, J. Frederick
Eliot, George Edwin 1864-1943
Fassett, J. Sloan
Fearson, George Randolph 1883-
Fess, Simeon Davidson 1861-1936
Finch, Edward Riley 1873-
Fish, Hamilton Jr. 1849-1936
Fisher, Irving 1867-1947
Fisher, Henry Johnson 1873-
Fiske, Bradley A 1854-1942
Fitch, Ashbel P. 1848-1904
Fleming, Matthew C. 1864-1946
Fletcher, Henry Prather 1873-1959
Flynn, Edward Joseph 1892-
Foley, James A. 1882-1946
Foote, Arthur E. 1853-1937
Forster, Rudolph
Fuchs, Emil E. 1866-1929
Furness, L
Galbraith, Archibald V.
Gerard, James Watson 1867-
Gilbert, Cass Jr. 1858-1934
Gildersleeve, Virginia Crockeron 1877-
Goodale, John
Goddard, Henry Warren 1876-
Goodman, Elias
Grant, DeForest 1869-
Griscom, Lloyd C.
Guthrie, William Dameron 1859-1935
Hackley, George R.
Hadley, Arthur Twining 1856-1930
Hadley, Helen Harrison (Morris) 1864-1939
Hagedorn, Hermann 1882-
Ha11, Samuel S., Jr.
Hammond, John Henry 1871-1949
Harbord, James Guthrie 1866-
Hart, Joseph G.
Hawkes, McDougall 1862-1929
Hayes, Will H 1879-1954
Hedges, Job Elmer 1862-1925
Herrick, Myron Timothy 1854-1929
Hess, Charles A.
Hewitt, Abram Stevens 1822-1903
Hibbard, Frederick, P.
Hibben, John Grier 1861-1933
Higgins, Frank Wayland 1856-1907
Hill, Albert S
Hill, David Jayne 1850-1932
Hill, George Edwin 1864-1916
Hilles, Charles Dewey 1867-1949
Hinman, George W., Jr.
Hitchcock, Frank Harris 1869-1935
Hogan, James M.
Hoover, Herbert Clark, Pres. U.S. 1874-
Houghton; Henry Martyn 1856-1910
House, Edward Mandall 1858-1938
Hoyt, Henry Martyn 1856-1910
Hoyt, John Sherman 1869-
Hughes, Charles Evans 1862-1948
Hughes, Charles Evans, Jr. 1853-1911
Hull, Cordell 1871-1955
Hurd, DeWitt C.
Hurley, Patrick Jay 1883-
James, Walter B. 1858-1927
Jennings, Oliver Gould 1865-1936
Jennings, Polly Brewster
Jennings, William Travers 1859-1934
Jerome, William Travers 1859-1934
Johnston, Henry Alan
Kean, Hamilton Fish 1862-1941
Kean, John 1852-1914
Kean, Julian H
Kellogg, Frank Billings 1856-1937
Kenlon, John 1859-1940
Ketcham, Henry B
King, Norman 1880-
Kirk, Alexander
Knox, Philander Chase 1853-1921
Keonig, Samuel S. 1872-
LaGuardia, Fiorello Henry 1882-1947
Lamm, Lewis
Lamont, Thomas William 1870-1948
Lane, Arthur Bliss 1894-1956
Laughlin, John
Leonard, Warren A
Lewis, Edwin A
Lewis, Richard J.
Lippmann, Walter 1889-
Lloyd, D. Frank
Lodge, Henry Cabot 1850-1924
Longworth, Nicholas 1869-1931
Lord, Benjamin
Low, Seth 1850-1916
Lowdenk Frank Omen 1861-1943
Maas, Charles O
Mackay, Clarence Hungerford 1874-1938
McKee, Joseph V 1889-
McClelland, Charles P. 1854-1944
McCook, Anson George 1835-1917
McCook, Philip James 1873
MacVeagh, Charlton
Mallory, W. Neely
Mansfield, Burton 1856-1932
Manton, Martin Thomas 1880-
Marks, Marcus M. 1858-1924
Marling, Alfred Erskine 1858-1935
Marling, Charles
Mason, Alexander T.
Massey, Vincent 1887-
Mayer, Julius M. 1865-1925
Mellon, Andrew William 1855-1937
Meyer, Eugene
Meyer, Otto A
Milbank, Albert G. 1873-1949
Miller, Chase Jr.
Miller, Nathan L. 1868-1953
Mills, Ogden Livingston 1884-1937
Monroe, Rolland G.
Moore, Elizabeth Putnam
More, Taylor
Morris, Robert Clark 1869-1938
Morrow, Dwight Whitney 1873-1931
Morrow, Elizabeth C. 1873-1935
Morton, Paul 1857-1911
Nally, Edward Julian 1859-
Nason, Daniel
Newberry, Truman Handy 1864-1945
North, Simon Newton Dexter 1849-1924
Norton, Henry Kittredge
Norton, Nathaniel
O'Brien, Morgan J. 1852-1937
Odell, Benjamin Barker 1854-1926
Olcott, J. VanVechten 1856-1940
Olds, Robert Edwin 1875-1938
Ovington, Specner O.M.
Parsons, Herbert 1869-1925
Patridge, Frank H.
Paulding, Charles C. 1868-1938
Penney, Thomas 1859-1933
Pepper, George Wharton 1867-
Perkins, George Wallbridge 1862-1920
Pershing, John Joseph 1860-1948
Phelps, John J. 1861-1948.
Phelps, William Lyon 1865-1943
Pinchot, Gifford 1865-1946
Polk, Frank Lyon 1871-1943
Pomeroy, Daniel Kleazer 1868-1946
Porter, Henry Hobert 1865-1947
Porter, John Addison 1856-1900
Porter, Joseph E.
Pratt, Ruth Sears (Baker) 1877-
Pritchard, Albert R.
Proctor, Thomas Redfield 1844-1920
Prosser, Seward 1871-1942
Quinby, Henry Cole 1872-1922
Recht, Charles 1870-
Reid, Helen Rogers 1882-
Reid, Whitelaw 1837-1912
Richards, Dickinson W.
Richards, William Roger 1853-1910
Robinson, Corrine Roosevelt 1861-1933
Robinson, Theodore Douglas 1883-
Roosevelt, Edith Kermit 1861-1948
Roosevelt, Eleanor 1884-1962
Roosevelt, Franklin Delano 1882-1945
Roosevelt, Theodore 1858-1919
Roosevelt, Theodore Jr. 1887-1944
Root, Elihu 1845-1937
Rowe, Leo Stanton 1871-1946
Rush, Thomas E
Russell, Charles Howland 1851-1921
Sampson Flex D.
Sands, Benjamin Aymar 1853-1917
Satterlee, Herbert Livingston 1863-1947
Schiff, Mortimer L. 1877-1931
Schoenfeld, Hans Frederick Arthur 1889-1952
Schwab, Gustva Henry 1851-1912
Schwab, John Christopher 1865-1916
Schwarz, F. A. O.
Scott, John Winfield
Shaw, James G.
Sheffield, Laura
Sheldon, George Rumsey
Shepherd, James G. 1838-1926
Sherman, James Schoolcraft 1855-1912
Sherman, M.S.
Sherman, Philemon Tecumsa 1867-
Shipman, Arthur L.
Simpson, Kenneth Farrand 1895-1941
Slater, Samuel S.
Sloan, Samuel
Sloane, William Mulligan 1850-1928
Smith, Alfred Emanuel 1873-1944
Smith, Howard C.
Snell, Bertrand H. 1870-1958
Stern, Louis
Stimson, Henry Lewis 1867-1950
Stoddard, Henry Luther 1861-
Stokes, Anson Phelps 1874-1958
Stortesbury, Louis W.
Strong, Charles Howard 1865-
Strong, William Lafayette 1827-1900
Sturgis, Thomas
Sturgis, Helen R.
Suares-Mujica, Eduardo 1859-
Swan, Thomas Walter 1877-
Swayne, Wager 1837-1902
Swope, Gerard
Taft, Henry W. 1859-1945
Taft, William Howard, Pres.U.S. 1857-1930
Tanner, Frederick C.
Thacher, Thomas Day 1881-1950
Thompson, William Boyce 1869-1930
Tolman, William Howe
Townsend, R. D.
Trevor, Clifford
Trevor, Emily N.
Trudeau, Edward Livingston 1848-1915
Underwood, Eugene Bertrand 1873-
Van Cott, Conrelius
Vanderbilt, Conrelius 1873-1942
Vanderlip, Frank Arthur 1864-1937
Vernon, Walter Newhall 1878-
Wadsworth, James Wolcott 1877-1952
Wagner, Robert Ferdinand 1877-1953
Walcott, Frederic Collin 1869-1949
Ward, George Cabot
Warner, B.H.
Warram, Noble
Watson, Clarence Wayland 1864-1940
Weddell, Alexander Wilbourne 1876-1948
Weeks, John Wingate 1860-1926
Welch, Lewis Sheldon 1867-1940
Wheeler, Everett
White, Edwin Douglass 1845-
White, William Pierrepont
Whitehouse, Sheldon 1883-
Whitman, Charles Seymour 1868-
Wickersham, George Woodward
Wiley, Louis 1869-1935
Williams, William 1862-1947
Williston, R. L.
Wilson, Hugh Robert 1885-
Winston, Frederick J.
Wood, Leonard 1860-1927
Woodward, George
Work, Hubert 1860-1942
Wright, Harry
Young, Owen D. 1874-1962
LETTERS FROM JAMES ROCKWELL SHEFFIELD TO:
Adee, George T. 1924 Sep 18
Aldridge, George W. 1921 Sep 21
Anderson, Chandler P. 1926 Mar 30; Apr 7, 26; May 14; Jun 1, 5; Nov 29 1927 Feb 11; Mar 7, 31; Apr 1, 22; May 3, 18 1928 Nov 1 1934 Aug 15
Anderson, Henry W. 1926 Apr 7, 28
Angell, James R. 1934 Aug 13
Austin, George C. 1921 Jan 4
Bainbridge, William Seuman 1934 Jun 20
Baker, Newton D. 1935 Jun 25
Bannard, Otto Tremont 1921 Jan 19
Bartlett, Philip G. 1922 Oct 21
Bonynge, Robert W. 1918 Oct 29
Borie, A.E. 1918 Feb 4
Brazier, John. H. 1893 Nov 9
Brownell, Herbert, Jr. 1934 Aug 13
Buckner, Mortimer N. 1924 Sep 18
Burleigh, George W. 1930 Apr 24
Burlingham, Charles C. 1928 Feb 7
Butler, Nicholas Murray 1912 Oct 22 1918 Jan 29 1919 May 8; Dec 8 1921 Mar 8 1924 Feb 18 1925 Nov 17 1927 Feb 11, 25; Mar 14 1930 Jan 6 1931 Nov 27 1932 Nov 30 1934 Aug 13 1935 Apr 1, 5, 15 1936 Apr 19; May 12 1937 Apr 28; Oct 7
Caffey, Francis G. 1923, Nov 28
Carter, George R. 1916 Apr 11
Castle, William R., Jr. 1931 Apr 1
Clark, John Kirkland 1928 Sep 20
Clarke, John Proctor 1923 Mar 27
Coffin, Henry S. 1918 Feb 6; May 7 1919 Mar 4
Coolidge, Calvin 1923 Aug 3 1927 Jul 19; Dec 27
Cooper, Vernon 1927 Jan 18
Coudert, Frderick R. 1938 Aug 22
Cowles, William H. 1938 Jan 3
Coxe, Alfred C. 1924 Jan 23
Crane, Frederick E. 1934 Feb 2
Cravath, Paul D. 1929 Apr 17
Curran, John E. 1923 Jan 11
Curtiss, Julian W. 1924 Sep 18
Damrosch, Margaret J. (Blaine) 1924: Jan 28; Mar 21
Davis, John W. 1934 Aug 13 1931 Sep 28 1937 Dec 3
Day, Ralph A. 1915 Dec 21 1923 Dec 14
Decker, William H. 1893 Nov 9
Depew, Chauncey Mitchell 1909 Oct 2
Dixon, John W. 1924 Sep 18
Dye, Alexander V. 1928 Dec 20
Fletcher, Henry P. 1934 Aug 13
Ford, Franklin 1928 Oct 5
Grant, Madison 1930 Jun 6
Gildersleeve, Virginia G. 1930 Nov 29 1933 Sep 29 1937 Oct 15; Nov 1
Guthrie, William D. 1934 May 28
Hagedorn, Hermann 1930 Nov 8
Harbord, James G. 1928 Nov 5 1930 Apr 21 1934 May 23 1937 Jun 10
Hibbard, Frederick P. 1927 Oct 24
Hilles, Charles D. 1917 Jun 26 1918 Oct 29 1919 Jan 3 1920 Feb 25 1921 Jan 20; Jul 13, 22 1922 Jul 20; May 2 1926 Jun 15 1932 May 23 1934 Apr 4 1936 Jan 3, 10; Mar 20
Hinman, George W. 1929 Jul 23 1932 Mar 15
Hitchcock, Mrs. Ripley 1928 Jan 17
Hodges, George W. 1923 Nov 19
Hoover, Herbert 1929 Jan 7
Houghton, Alanson B. 1928 Dec 20
Hoyt, Henry Martyn 1906 Oct 24
Hughes, Charles Evans 1924 Aug 15 1930 Feb 13 1934 Aug 14 1937 Oct 4
Hull, Cordell 1935 Sep 18
Jennings, Annie B. 1934 Dec 13
Jennings, Oliver G. 1929 Dec 30 1936 Jun 15
Kellog, Frank B. 1926 Jul 1 1928 Jul 18; Dec 28 1934 Jan 10; Aug 13
Kellog, Frederic R. 1929 Oct 10
Knox, Philander Chase 1908 Dec 19
Koenig, Samuel S. 1924 Feb 9 1933 Sep 26
Lamont, Thomas W. 1931 Nov 6 1934 Aug 13 1935 Oct 28
Lane, Arthur Bliss 1928 Apr 28; May 31; Nov 27 1934 Aug 15
Lawrence, William E. 1921 Dec 15 1934 Aug 15
Lippmann, Walter 1931 Sep 23
Lowden, Franke O. 1935 Jun 10
Mack, Walter s. 1933 Feb 9
Macy, W. Kingland 1934 Sep 21
MacKay, Clarence H. 1938 Apr 19
Marconi, G. 1928 Feb 4
Mason, Julian S. 1927 Oct 21
Mellen, Chase, Jr. 1934 Dec 11, 20, 24 1933 Dec 18
Menken, S. Stanwood 1932 Feb 8
Mitchell, John Murray 1895 Apr 27
Moore, Thomas M. 1917 Jan 2
Morrow, Dwight W. 1920 Apr 29 1923 Aug 9; Nov 27; Dec 7 1927 Oct 3; Nov 17 1928 Apr 16 1929 Aug 1 1931 Mar 19; May 20
Meyer, Eugene 1936 May 27
Murphy, James J. 1893 Nov 2
Nettleton, George H. 1934 Aug
Newberry, Truman Handy 1908 Nov 17
O'Brien, Morgan Joseph 1924 Oct 3 1935 May 8
Olds, Robert E. 1927 Oct 24 Nov 15; Dec 21, 22, 27
Perkins, George W. 1911 Aug 7, 26; Oct 27 1912 Mar 16
Phelps, William L 1925 Oct 3; Nov 12 1934 Aug 16
Pierce, Palmer S. 1927 Nov 2
Pinchot, Amos Richards Eno 1910 Aug 19
Pinchot, Gifford 1910 Jan 8
Polk, Frank L. 1934 Aug 14
Pomeroy, Daniel E. 1922 May 9
Porter, H. Hobart 1929 Feb 5
Pritchett, Henry S. 1928 Dec 26
Reid, Ogden 1936 Apr 27
Reusswig, Fred E. 1916 Jun 13
Roosevelt, Edith Kermit (Carow) 1905?
Root, Elihu 1927 Oct 31 1928 Mar 9 1929 Jul 29; Aug 16 1930 Jan 13, 16, 1931 Feb 11 1933 Feb 15; May 24; Jun 23 1934 Feb 15; Jul 3; Aug 13 1935 Sep 25; Oct 31; Dec 17 1936 May 17; Dec 30
Root, Elihu, Jr. 1937 Feb 17; Mar 13
Rothstein, David King 1936 Nov 25
Rundell, Mrs. Will A. 1927 Feb 3
Sargent, John G. 1929 Jun 28
Sarnoff, David 1934 Aug 14
Saunders, William F. 1928 Jul 11
Schoenfeld, H. F. Arthur 1927 Feb 1, 7, 15, 21; Mar 1, 7 1929 Apr 4 1931 Jan 2 1934 Aug 15 1938 Aug 22
Sebaste, Archbishop of (Caruana, George) 1926 Nov 29
Sheffield, Sarah Kellogg 1901 Sep 8 1912 Jun 22; Jul 13, 20; Aug 3 1915 Feb 13
Simpson, Kenneth F. 1935 Oct 16
Smith, Alfred E. 1934 Aug 14
Stevens, Guy 1928 Dec 28
Stimson, Henry Lewis 1934 Oct 9 1929 Mar 26; Apr 6; May 16
Stoddard, Henry Luther 1912 Jul 31
Stokes, Anson Phelps 1928 Feb 8
Stryker, Lloyd Paul 1929 Sep 6
Taft, Henry Waters 1907 Mar 21
Taft, William Howard 1927 Jan 7, 28; Feb 9; Mar 5, 24; Apr 22 1928 Jun 4, 12 1930 Feb 13
Thacher, Thomas Day 1934 Aug 22
Townsend, James B. 1893 Oct 23
Vanamee, Grace (Davis) 1921 Feb 12
Vanderbilt, Cornelius 1934 Aug 13
Wadsworth, James W., Jr. 1926 Mar 4; Apr 7, 14; Jun 3; Dec 3 1927 Nov 3 1934 Aug 13
Weddell, Alexander W. 1927 Dec 5 1934 Aug 14
Weeks, John Wingate 1921 Dec 30 1924 Jun 13
Welch, Herbert 1903 May 16